{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "She ___ to school every day.",
      "options": [
        "go",
        "going",
        "goes ",
        "gone"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
     {
      "question": "I ___ dinner when she arrived.",
      "options": [
        "had",
        "am having",
        "was having  ",
        "have had"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "They ___ in Mumbai since 2015.",
      "options": [
        "lived",
        "have been living",
        "lives",
        "are living"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "He ___ already left when I got there.",
      "options": [
        "has",
        "have",
        "had",
        "was"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "By next year, she ___ her degree.",
      "options": [
        "completes",
        "completed",
        "will complete",
        "will have completed"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The sun ___ in the east.",
      "options": [
        "rise",
        "rises",
        "is rising",
        "has risen"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "I ___ him yesterday at the mall.",
      "options": [
        "saw",
        "see",
        "have seen",
        "had seen"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "While we ___ TV, the lights went out.",
      "options": [
        "watch",
        "were watching",
        "watched",
        "had watched"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "She usually ___ tea in the evening.",
      "options": [
        "drinking",
        "drinks",
        "drank",
        "has drunk"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "They ___ for two hours before the rain stopped.",
      "options": [
        "had been walking",
        "have walked",
        "walked",
        "were walking"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "I think it ___ soon.",
      "options": [
        "rained",
        "is raining",
        "will rain",
        "rains"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "She ___ to Delhi tomorrow.",
      "options": [
        "goes",
        "going",
        "will go",
        "go"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "He ___ a lot of books when he was young.",
      "options": [
        "read",
        "has read",
        "reads",
        "reading"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "I ___ this book for three days.",
      "options": [
        "am reading",
        "have been reading",
        "had read",
        "read"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "We ___ for you since morning.",
      "options": [
        "are waiting",
        "were waiting",
        "have been waiting",
        "wait"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The train ___ before we reached the station.",
      "options": [
        "left",
        "had left",
        "leaves",
        "has left"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "By 8 p.m., they ___ dinner.",
      "options": [
        "ate",
        "eating",
        "eat",
        "will have eaten "
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "He ___ already finished his homework.",
      "options": [
        "have",
        "has",
        "is",
        "was"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "We ___ this place when we were kids.",
      "options": [
        "visit",
        "visited",
        "visiting",
        "have visited"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": " I___ to London next week.",
      "options": [
        "fly",
        "was flying",
        "am flying",
        " have flown"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The children ___ when the bell rang.",
      "options": [
        "were playing",
        "played",
        "are playing",
        "play"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "She ___ her homework already.",
      "options": [
        "done",
        "has done",
        "did",
        "doing"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "We ___ the match if we had practiced more.",
      "options": [
        "won",
        "win",
        "would have won",
        "will win"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": " He said he ___ the letter.",
      "options": [
        "writes",
        "will write",
        "had written",
        "is writing"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": " She ___ to learn French for a year.",
      "options": [
        "is trying",
        "has been trying",
        "tries",
        "try"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    }
  ]
}
